Hello, I'm Aina, your interviewer, and I'll be talking to you today.
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, student number 5 from Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
Pleased to meet you.
Wow, you started like a proper interviewer.
Just the beginning?
I'm going to start from the beginning, so let's start from the beginning.
Rough.
Roughly.
So, Shiritsu Ebisu celebrates its 15th anniversary this year.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Looking back over the past 15 years
I'm going to ask you a question right away.
Is there any particular scene that has left a deep impression on you?
I wonder.
But I guess, after 15 years of Ebitubers, we've had a lot of members.
There have been many graduations and new members have joined.
The timing of those milestones are always memorable.
I'm sure that the new members will have the same enthusiasm to become a new Ebituaroo that everyone loves.
and the feeling of support for the departing members, so such a milestone live is always memorable for me.
I think it's really great that we have been reduced from 3BJr.
We have been reduced from 3BJr. but we have never had any new members,
I see.
I always tell the members that if a new member came in, we would never be able to speak well together,
I always tell the members that if a new member joins the group, we would never be able to talk well together, but at Ebinaka-san, everyone gets along very well, even if a new member, such as Cocona, or a young junior member, joins,
I have the image of them having a great time talking together,
Is there something you are conscious of, Ayaka?
Ah, but I'm sure I've been aware of that since I was very young.
I'm conscious of creating an environment where it's easy for newcomers to say what they want to say.
The existing girls who are still here are quite pacifistic.
And the existing older sisters who are still here are pretty pacifistic and like to have fun, so I think that's why they've been able to stay as innocent as they were when they were little.
The older sisters who are still innocent and happy are coming in.
I felt like my sister and her sisters were very strong and proper.
I think that's why we have a lot of customers because of my sister's personality and character.
I think a lot of our customers are here because of the personalities and character of all my sisters.
Are there any popular games? There are still students, aren't there?
We've all graduated, so I don't really know what's trendy.
I wonder... I wonder if it's a fad... but in that sense, my sisters who are students might not be so familiar with the latest trends.
Surprisingly.
Cocona has her own favorites, but...
I ask her what's trendy.
I don't know.
She might say she doesn't know.
Cocona has a friend who is a gal, and her friend says that there is a certain type of fort that is popular amongst the gals.
I'm sure it's just in that area, but I'd love to hear about it. I'm sure that the matchage refort is delicious, but I had no idea that it was a fad.
I'm also really imagining what it would be like to go into Ibichu-san.
I'm really shy, so I wondered if it would be difficult for me to talk to people even if I'm 5 years older than them.
I guess I don't have to worry about it.
They seem to be having a lot of fun. They're always so lively. It's just too noisy.
I see... I see that the members haven't changed at all from 15 years ago.
Or, on the other hand, has anything changed? Is there anyone you dream about?
Well, I guess... But in terms of 15 years, the one who has been here the longest is Maya.
Until Maya. Maya has never really changed.
Because Mayama never changes.
I think that's why they say you don't change.
You don't even change your appearance.
And the way you think about things...
and the way I feel about EBITCHU...
I can follow you because of that.
I feel like she's the oldest sister, she's so cool.
I feel like I'm getting younger and younger... that's what people often say to me... that everyone in Ebinaka is like that... but maybe that's true.
I feel like I'm getting younger and younger because I'm feeling the student's movement as the younger members are moving in, and I'm really wearing the uniform, so I guess I'm always feeling young.
I always thought that was amazing.
She is getting younger and younger and more beautiful.
But the kids who were the same age as me, the stapler kids, they were just little kids, and now they are all grown up.
That's right.
Most of them are over 20 years old now?
Almost all of them.
That's right.
Hana will turn 20 this February.
So, when we get together for lessons and rehearsals at STAPRO, the atmosphere is totally different from before,
That's true.
It's an adult atmosphere, so I feel like I'm the only one left out.
I feel like, "Oh no, oh no, everyone is doing everything right, so I have to do it right too.
I feel like I'm not being left out.
I'm so happy to see that everyone has become older sisters.
I'm so happy. I'm so surprised.
I was really surprised to see that at last year's staff festival. I was so surprised to see that at last year's Staff La Fest as well.
Thank you very much. Now that I'm finally 20 years old, I've been thinking that I'd like to get closer to you, and I've been trying my best to talk to you.
I'd love to talk to you. I'd like to take this opportunity to go out with you privately.
I'd love to go out with you.
But I'm really bad at asking people out.
I will invite you.
Please invite me.
I'll do my best. I'm not good at inviting people, but I'll do it.
You look like you're in some kind of caste.
It certainly looks that way from the front.